=The Origin of Eternity=
= أصل الخلود =
=Episode 1=
= الحلقة 1 =
It has been ten thousand years
لقد مرت عشرة آلاف سنة
since you ascended as an immortal.
منذ أن صعدت كخالد.
After experiencing three lifetimes of tribulations in the mortal world,
بعد تجربة ثلاث مراحل من الضيقات في العالم الفاني ،
you'll definitely ascend to the Heavenly Palace
ستصعد بالتأكيد إلى القصر السماوي
as the Heavenly Emperor.
مثل الإمبراطور السماوي.
The position of the Heavenly Emperor is not what I want.
منصب الإمبراطور السماوي ليس ما أريده.
Facing tribulations in the mortal world is even more unnecessary.
إن مواجهة المحن في العالم الفاني ليست ضرورية أكثر.
Now, don't be too mean with your words.
الآن ، لا تكن لئيمًا جدًا بكلماتك.
Fate had already been decided.
كان القدر قد تقرر بالفعل.
We only wait for it to realize.
نحن ننتظر فقط حتى يدرك ذلك.
Immortal Bai Ze, you sure have a profound cultivation.
الخالد باي زي ، لديك بالتأكيد زراعة عميقة.
With just a slight touch of your robe,
بمجرد لمسة خفيفة من رداءك ،
the iris has taken the form of a human.
اتخذت القزحية شكل الإنسان.
It's something to celebrate about.
إنه شيء يستحق الاحتفال به.
Not only do you look handsome,
لا تبدو وسيمًا فحسب ،
but your name is also nice.
لكن اسمك جميل ايضا.
I'm Qinghuan.
أنا كينغوان.
Immortal Bai Ze, wait for me.
الخالد باي زي ، انتظرني.
Speaking of fate,
بالحديث عن القدر
his fate is here.
مصيره هنا.
This will be interesting.
سيكون هذا ممتعًا.
Immortal Bai Ze.
الخالد باي زي.
Why do you keep following me?
لماذا تستمر في متابعتي؟
You transformed me into an immortal.
لقد حولتني إلى خالد.
I would naturally set my mind on you
من الطبيعي أن أضع عقلي عليك
and serve you
وخدمتك
forever.
للأبد.
I didn't mean to transform you.
لم أقصد أن أحولك.
I don't need you to serve me too.
لا أريدك أن تخدمني أيضًا.
From now on, don't show up in front of me.
من الآن فصاعدا ، لا تظهر أمامي.
What?
ماذا؟
Immortal Bai Ze!
الخالد باي زي!
She's pretty persistent in following you for the past year.
إنها مثابرة جدًا على متابعتك طوال العام الماضي.
♪Wandered off from the crowd♪
تجول بعيدًا عن الحشد ♪
♪As more wonderful things await♪
♪ كما تنتظر المزيد من الأشياء الرائعة
♪A sunset from the past resurfaced♪
انعكاس غروب الشمس من الماضي
♪Thousands of sailboats drifted in the sea of clouds♪
جرفت آلاف المراكب الشراعية في بحر السحب
Immortal Bai Ze.
الخالد باي زي.
♪Only the catkin willow and my graying hair remained♪
فقط صفصاف القطة وشعري الشيب بقي
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I want to give you this peach.
أريد أن أعطيك هذا الخوخ.
♪I traveled alone toward daytime as I waved aside the night♪
سافرت لوحدي في النهار بينما كنت ألوح جانباً في الليل
♪The tapping rain♪
مطر التنصت ♪
Since I transformed you into an immortal,
منذ أن حولتك إلى خالدة
why don't you cherish this opportunity
لماذا لا تعتز بهذه الفرصة
and start cultivating?
والبدء في الزراعة؟
I've already started cultivating.
لقد بدأت بالفعل في الزراعة.
Tonight is the night I'll undergo the thunder tribulation.
الليلة هي الليلة التي سأخوض فيها بضيق الرعد.
After you've finished this peach,
بعد الانتهاء من هذا الخوخ ،
you'll be able to see me.
ستتمكن من رؤيتي.
♪After you overcome the vicissitudes of life♪
بعد أن تتغلب على تقلبات الحياة
Immortal Bai Ze.
الخالد باي زي.
If I pass this tribulation,
إذا مررت بهذه الضيقة ،
would you praise me?
هل تمدحني
The thunder tribulation is nothing more than this.
محنة الرعد ليست أكثر من هذا.
Why is it not over yet?
لماذا لم ينته بعد؟
I can't hold on anymore.
لا أستطيع الصمود بعد الآن.
♪The time was fleeting away before the iris wilted♪
كان الوقت يمر بعيدًا قبل أن تذبل القزحية ♪
♪But we made a promise for this life♪
♪ لكننا قطعنا وعدًا لهذه الحياة ♪
♪I couldn't free myself from the entanglement of love♪
♪ لم أستطع تحرير نفسي من ورطة الحب ♪
♪I didn't want to see a tearful farewell♪
♪ لم أرغب في رؤية وداع باكي ♪
♪I was obsessed with love of the past♪
♪ كنت مهووسًا بحب الماضي ♪
♪If only I could first see you in the next life♪
♪ لو كان بإمكاني رؤيتك أولاً في الحياة التالية ♪
♪I wish we could be together again♪
♪ أتمنى أن نكون معًا مرة أخرى ♪
♪For another thousand years♪
♪ لألف سنة أخرى ♪
You pester me all day.
أنت تضايقني طوال اليوم.
How can you survive the tribulation?
كيف يمكنك النجاة من الضيقة؟
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
I owe it to you.
أنا مدين لك.
♪I turn into the gentle mist and caress your face♪
♪ أتحول إلى ضباب لطيف وأداعب وجهك
♪Will we bid goodbye to each other after singing the farewell ballad?
♪ هل نودع بعضنا البعض بعد غناء أغنية الوداع؟
♪I turn into the snow to freeze fickleness♪
♪ ألتفت إلى الثلج لتجميد التقلبات ♪
It's all on you now.
كل شيء عليك الآن.
♪Wandered off from the crowd♪
تجول بعيدًا عن الحشد ♪
♪As more wonderful things await♪
♪ كما تنتظر المزيد من الأشياء الرائعة
♪A sunset from the past resurfaced♪
انعكاس غروب الشمس من الماضي
♪Thousands of sailboats drifted in the sea of clouds♪
جرفت آلاف المراكب الشراعية في بحر السحب
♪And docked at different piers♪
♪ ورست على أرصفة مختلفة ♪
♪Only the catkin willow and my graying hair remained♪
فقط صفصاف القطة وشعري الشيب بقي
♪Let's take on♪
♪ لنأخذ
♪Another year♪
♪ سنة أخرى ♪
♪I traveled alone toward daytime as I waved aside the night♪
سافرت لوحدي في النهار بينما كنت ألوح جانباً في الليل
♪The tapping rain♪
مطر التنصت ♪
♪Awakened the sorrow♪
أيقظ الحزن
♪I'm crying out in loneliness amid pandemonium♪
♪ أنا أبكي في عزلة وسط الهرج والمرج
♪I endured countless ordeals from worldly entanglement♪
لقد تحملت محن لا حصر لها من التشابك الدنيوي ♪
♪Knowing how difficult things are for the first time♪
معرفة مدى صعوبة الأمور لأول مرة ♪
♪When you overcome the vicissitudes of life♪
عندما تتغلب على تقلبات الحياة
♪Only then you understand the fickleness of the world♪
"عندها فقط تفهم تقلب العالم"
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪